October's own is the label. Self-figure
deal was a fable. Eight-figure bought
out the neighbors. Now figure's turning
the tables. You boy better be
ready and able. I'm coming. I can't talk
on my old case cuz it's sticky. [music]
Free T and free Greasy, my killies. My
youngest put loss [singing] on the city
so be scared to come out when
it's litty.
See that's the quality [music] so free
of these are joking. I wouldn't
want to be in my beat a producer like
what's the BPM? I cannot de-escalate
things that we seeing. My young boys
don't do [music] it for clout. If
[singing] they do it, they cover they
head and they mouth. Swear there's some
I'm forgetting about. 03 was the
slime when they letting him out. I'll be
with them guys on the six that you
they talking [music] all written
about. Say a whole lot but we saw you
[singing] and we had you begging it out.
Remember that [music] Twist.
Twisting it.
Yeah, twisting his fingers and looking
at me. Twisting some up that I
never seen. Twisting it up. I don't know
what that means. Twist. [music]
I'm twisting it back cuz he twisting at
me. Twisting that six in his face.
Twisting it.
Welcome, ladies and gentlemen, to this
video. How I made a little over half a
million dollars and how I used that
money to help me pay
for the famous Bugatti. And uh you know,
a little things of here of the trading
floor. So this this is our two biggest
prize possessions that we have as of
right now. It doesn't look very
prize possession to me.
>> Dude, this is like
both up.
>> [laughter]
>> Like they're both They literally look
the same.
>> identical. The trading floor this this
So this is our HQ. This is our
headquarters. Uh I'm building a big
compound down here in Miami. We'll talk
a little bit more about that later. And
then my Bugatti. And they're both
up. They're both incomplete.
>> Do you know what they also have in
common? What?
>> They both don't have lights. Oh, you're
right. Let's show them the front. So
parts of the half a million dollars that
I made went towards some parts like our
headlights. So we actually found a
solution with the headlights and talk
about that later in the video and other
parts of it. But I want to start off
this video with breaking down the actual
trade that led me to make half What was
it? 500 and
3,500 4,000? I have no idea. Those
numbers are way too big for me to
remember. Something like that. Honestly,
I don't know. Let me show you guys break
down the trade. And this is a live
trade. I can show you about, I don't
know, a thousand of my students that
caught the exact same trade. So, this
right here
This is the trade. So, this is GBP CAD
that I made $503,000.
As you guys can see, this is a real live
account. You guys can go verify that
account number. And this is a real
trade. So, this trade was actually
pretty unique because it happened on a
Friday. I don't typically take trades on
a Friday. And I actually want to show
you guys the results of my students in
my community. This is like not even a
promo to my community, but just to show
you that I'm not the only person that
actually executes these trades. So, this
is actually 7 days ago that I actually
entered this position. So, this is GBP
CAD. And I posted "Post your profits.
Patience pays." So, these are all of the
students that actually entered this
position as well in my community. For
example, you have this student that made
500 bucks on this account. And he made
about $400 on his other account. You
have this student that made
Wow.
This dude made three grand. This guy
should take us out for lunch, no?
>> Dude, I didn't even get a piece of that.
Dude, look at this guy.
This guy made $9,000, bro.
What the dude?
How come we never get like gifts What
what like that no one takes us out to
eat or nothing like
>> What like why is no one like giving us
anything, bro?
Like why are we helping people and no
one is helping us? [snorts]
I don't know.
Like I should almost like ask for a
percentage of it, right? Yeah. I mean
You're kind of the one that taught them.
Wow.
Well, I mean I should get a percentage
too cuz I'm I'm I'm the reason why they
even see it.
>> what? You're right. And that's exactly
why we built this trading floor.
>> [laughter]
>> No, honestly, that's exactly why we
built it because we're going to have
traders in here manage funds and I will
get a little piece of it. You know, if I
teach you how to be profitable and you
make money from it, the least you can do
is, you know, give Uncle Alex G, you
know, a little little little something.
So, let me break down this trade because
this is actually a beautiful trade. Now,
this is going to go for beginners,
intermediates, advanced. This is going
to make sense right off the bat because
it's just a very simple trade. And
honestly, I was not supposed to make
that much money and I'm going to explain
why, right? So, this is GBP/CAD. So, I
actually took this trade last week. And
the beauty of GBP/CAD is that it was
consolidating at this support level. So,
right now we're on the 4-hour time
frame. It was accumulating at this area
for about
about 15 days. So, we were stuck in this
range for 15 days. And for me, whenever
I see a market that is stuck in a range
like this, I wait for two things. Either
a breakout to the downside to then sell
or a breakout to the upside to then buy.
So, that's exactly what this market did
right here at this very moment. So, I
literally drew this up at the beginning
of the weekend and I'm like, I'm waiting
for the breakout, the famous retest, and
then the continuation. So, then price
breaks out of this range. As soon as we
break out of it, I then head over to the
daily time frame. And on the daily time
frame, I confirm that that breakout is
legit because of the closure of the
daily candlestick. As you can tell, this
candlestick right here, when it was
inside of this range for an approximate
9 days, this candlestick did break above
that consolidation zone, but it closed
below. So, this candlestick right here
actually ended up breaking above and
closing above this massive consolidation
right here, which is perfect. Now, what
do I do after that? I go back down to
the lower time frames. I'm like, all
right, cool. I'm now going to wait for
price to come back and give me the
famous retracements because without the
retracement, you don't want to just
enter on the breakout. That's why it's
called
the break and retest. It's almost as if
Bitcoin were to hit brand new all-time
highs, right? Let's say Bitcoin right
now goes to $200,000.
Which would be phenomenal
for our portfolio. That would be
awesome. But, for some reason
beginners or rookies, they like buying
at the new all-time high. They get FOMO.
They think that price is going to go and
shoot up to 300,000 right away. That's
not really the case. What ends up
happening is after a price always has a
push to the upside, it will always have
a little bit of a retracement to then
continue going to the upside. That's the
higher low, what I like to call the
discount. So, picture this right here as
price breaking out into this high.
Picture Bitcoin hitting 200,000, me not
buying at 200,000 because it's just way
too expensive, waiting for a little bit
of a retracement, and that's where it
retests the exact same area that it was
trapped in. So, as you can tell,
whenever we're below, we head down.
Whenever we're below, we head down.
We're below, we head down. We head down.
And here we're above. And if I just look
to the left, the last time we were above
this area we clearly went up. So, it's
very simple. We're consolidating at an
area. We break above. The daily confirms
that we close above. And we're coming
back to retest the exact same area where
we've previously had a literal reaction.
Now, when you add to that my EMA, so
just for a lot of you guys that want to
see my EMA, I'm just going to double
click it here. This is the settings to
my EMA.
It's a 50 close offset zero. The length
is 1.4 BB STD.
What the What is that? What is
STD?
STD dev.
You got two STD STDs. I got two of them.
Oh.
That would suck, bro.
>> [laughter]
>> I don't have any of that.
But whatever that is, it's two. I don't
I've never set that up. I always
set these up in this area right here.
So, what I saw is that price was above
this consolidation zone, retested it.
It's above our EMA, and then we have the
most beautiful bullish engulfing morning
star formation pattern happening right
there. That is the exact entry that I
look for when I'm having a retracement.
So, to enter a breakout trade, a trend
continuation trade, you either want to
have a rejection candlestick or an
engulfing candlestick. When you have
those combined, they can form what is
called a morning star or evening star
formation. Morning star meaning up,
evening star meaning down. Now, this
morning star formation is by far my
favorite.
I entered the trade, put my stop loss at
an area where it was significant, but
not that significant, and then my take
profit was actually at this point right
here. So, I wanted my take profit to be
at the nearest structure point. Because
if I go out to the daily timeframe,
right, if I were to just remove all of
the price that has currently happened,
when I entered the position, the daily
timeframe looked like this. And I
measured my entry point, which is right
around here, to my take profit. And I'm
like, "Okay, cool. I'm going to get this
movement that I'm anticipating to happen
on Friday because I never take trades
Thursday London session heading to
Friday because there's not enough
volume. But I'm like, "Let me see what
the average daily volume is." Now,
there's a bunch of indicators out there
to do it, but there's nothing like
literally measuring the exact
candlesticks. So, for example, if I look
at the previous daily candlestick, it
has that exact same size. If I measure
this candlestick, this candlestick is a
lot bigger. Even this small doji is of
that size, is of that size, is of that
size, is of that size. Every single
candlestick that has been in here for
the last 15 days in the consolidation is
of the size that I need for it to go
from my entry point to my take profit.
So, it's very possible. Now, if I if I
were to look left, all of this momentum
over here is far larger than what I
need. So, I said, "Okay, cool. Perfect."
For me, it makes sense to enter the
trade and have my take profit be at that
point right there. But
you guys know I live by the saying,
set and forget. What does that mean? I
enter a position and I forget about it.
Literally, sometimes too much and it
actually ends up biting me in the ass,
but there's times where stuff like this
happens. So, I enter the position in
London session. As soon as I enter the
position, after my engulfing
candlestick, I go to sleep and I
immediately go straight to my take
profit. But, the beauty of it is since I
don't set my take profit numbers,
instead of me closing at a 1:2 risk to
reward, I automatically jumped straight
to nearly a 1:4 on this position right
here. So, by the time that I wake up in
the morning, I'm seeing this trade be a
lot more profit than I should be. And
that's simply because I'm letting a
winning position continue to run. I'm I
don't want to cut my wins short. Never,
at all. I always want to cut my losses
short because that means that I would
have been wrong. If I do my top-down
analysis correctly, why would I want to
cut my win short? It's almost like if
Bitcoin
goes to 200,000, has a retracement to
150,000, and it gives you the perfect
entry, why would you want to
liquidate your Bitcoin at 200,000 again?
You would anticipate for it to go to
220, 240,000, and it continues to the
upside. This is no different than that.
I don't know why people treat it
differently. But, this trade, I continue
to hold it until about 11:00 in the
morning, and then I close my position
right around here, right around like a
1:4.
And uh
yeah. The rest is history. I was not
supposed to make half a million dollars.
I was supposed to probably make like
200,
like 220,
and it ended up playing out in our
favor. So, this is a perfect example of
set and forget.
And now we get that money and we spend
it, all of it.
On unfinished projects. Oh, dude, but
they haven't seen the withdrawal.
No, they haven't.
>> So, it's not real.
Should I Fugazi. Oh, dude, I have to
request a withdrawal. Fugazi, figazi.
>> Oh, man,
they caught me, bro. It's demo money,
bro.
>> [sighs]
>> It's a joke.
>> [laughter]
>> Obviously, bro. I just haven't requested
it yet. Now, yes, I have not withdrawn
the half a million dollars. So,
technically, no, I have not made that
money yet. It's still in my account, but
I have withdrawn in the past. And yes,
it's still the exact same account number
for all of the freaks out there. The
reason why I haven't withdrawn is
because I entered a 2-month losing
streak at the beginning of the year. And
that I want to create an extra cushion
in my account just in case if now going
into the summer markets, for whatever
reason the markets are slow, and I can
potentially enter another losing streak,
I have that cushion, and I don't
redeposit into my account, and I'm not
having to dig myself out of a massive
hole. I hate redepositing into account.
I'm so superstitious that I'd rather
create a brand new account rather than
deposit back into the same account. So,
yeah, I don't redeposit back into it,
and I'd rather just leave it in there,
get a bigger cushion, then withdraw, and
see how summer goes by because typically
the markets are usually slower during
the summer. So, I'm just preparing,
learning from my experience.
So, yeah, this is a beautiful half a
million dollar trade. And after I exited
the position, and I did not get greedy,
the trade came back into where our entry
and our stop loss would have been. So,
this trade was executed to perfection.
This is exactly how a trade should be
entered
and exited. That is a perfect entry,
perfect exit. So, now let's get to the
point.
What's the point? The Bugatti. Oh, you
don't care You don't care about the
trade that helps us afford the Bugatti?
No. Oh, you're just one of Matt
Armstrong's fans that just cares about
the Bugatti.
That is just in the comments, "Oh, I'm
just here for the Bugatti."
Fine. You know, there's a lot more to us
than just a Bugatti, guys, you know?
[clears throat]
No, I can't Matt Armstrong's community
would kill me.
>> [laughter]
>> All right, let me Should we put it
outside? So, there's a little bit more
lighting? I I actually like the lighting
in here. It's cinematic. Does it look
cinematic?
>> Yeah. Add in some chill music right now,
like some cinematic
>> [music]
>> Did you do it? Yeah. You did it? Yeah,
it's done.
Well, you know what else is not done?
The Bugatti.
So, the car is officially put together.
So, we've actually driven it at pretty
high speeds. I think we've gone
like 130 miles an hour, and it's very
crazy because there's no windshield on
the car. So, all the wind obviously
comes in, smacks you right in the face,
eat some bugs. It's like the Elva, but
worse. Yes. For those of you guys that
don't know, I had a McLaren Elva.
Worst hypercar I've owned in my
life.
Biggest waste of money. I lost $300,000
on that car.
Can you believe that?
I thought I was doing something cool,
and then
I look like an idiot
in a pink and green car. That was
terrible. But, all we are literally
missing on this car is literally the
headlights,
the body kit that we got for it,
the windshield, and the roof.
Now, I want to tell you guys something
right now. If you guys were to see the
body kit that this car has,
I am lost for words. Let's just say this
is really going to be a one-of-one
Bugatti. That That's really all I have
to say. I was thinking, what if we
remake the Bugatti logo and we use our
own logo?
Don't you think we could get sued for
that? No.
I mean, we haven't gotten sued up to
this point.
>> Yeah. Honestly, I don't want to jinx it.
Yeah, we'll leave it in the video, but
you know, I I don't want to jinx it. So,
actually earlier, we were actually
driving the car pretty hard, and the
heat soak from this exhaust is pretty
ridiculous. If it wouldn't be for these
heat shields,
all of this right here would 100%
definitely melt. This exhaust gets
extremely hot, or maybe we were just
driving it that hard. But, this sounds
good,
but it doesn't sound the
crazy SVJ what I expected, you know? It
was a disappointing. So, everything on
the car is pretty much on that could be
on aside from obviously basic quarter
panels. You have the rear wing which the
new wing
Oh, did I just destroy something? I
guess we did. Well,
it's going to be crazy.
Interior. Oh, look, dude, the doors the
the lights still work.
Oh, wow.
Dude, they survived the crash. They
survived all this.
Where would if if this if that would
have broken, where would we have bought
that?
eBay? I think eBay has that. Yeah, 100%.
The Chiron Pur Sport light. Yeah, why
wouldn't they? I mean, you're right.
Half the car is Volkswagen anyways,
right?
Oh.
Well, we should low-key get this car out
of here, bro.
Well, actually, you know what's pretty
ironic? There is going to we actually
strategically left a parking spot for a
car in here once we're done with the
trading floor. So, there is going to be
just a parking spot for a one car to be
right in there. And it's kind of cool
that you guys are seeing the journey of
this because you're seeing this get
made. You're seeing this get built. And
then you're going to see them both at
the same exact time, which is pretty
cool that you guys are part of it at
this time. Honestly, we we should take
it outside. Oh, before we take it
outside,
traders.
We are looking for traders.
As you can see here, we have about 12
different trading desks inside of our
trading floor for people that are
successful. So, people inside of our
community obviously have a major
priority in terms of being part of the
trading floor. And yes, we have a
strict way in order to enter the trading
floor. Obviously, results will be the
driving factor of it, but I also want to
have a hybrid. I want half of this
section to be successful profitable
traders and this half to not be
successful traders. And everybody's
going to be in teams and whichever coach
can make the unprofitable trader
profitable on their own will win
something. We're going to have
competitions and lots of cool things
that we're going to be doing inside of
the Swing Trading Lab trading floor. You
know, we're kind of just still figuring
out the ways of it, but don't worry,
everybody's going to have a chance to
come here, be part of this experience
and what we're building here. We're
almost done. It might not look like it's
done, but we're actually very close to
being done. I'd probably give it what?
Like 24 hours?
24 hours?
>> No. No.
I wish. I wish I could just click a
button and then this should be done. No,
but I'd probably give it realistically
another 2 weeks.
Yeah, I mean, it's already taking shape.
Yeah. Compared to what it was before
when you started.
>> Yeah, so this area over here is going to
be like the kitchen area. There's going
to be a kitchen over there, lounge area,
TV. Ah, and then we have the second
floor, which we'll save for later. I
feel like we've never named her.
She's been like the Bugatti.
And that is the Bugatti. Is that Is that
the name? The Bugatti? I mean, it is the
most famous Bugatti. I think it is the
most famous Bugatti. I think that's the
name.
The Bugatti.
>> The Bugatti. I like that.
Well, let's take out
the Bugatti.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Wow.
The Bugatti. I like that.
I like that.
I've actually burned my leg with this
right here so many times already. So,
this
is a very hot pipe. I don't know what
that connects to. What is this? The
That's like for the radiator. This is
the radiator? Yeah.
>> You sure? One of the radiators. Cuz that
looks like the fuel pump.
>> Or oil radiators. Oil radiators.
>> Yeah. Well, whatever this is, it gets
extremely hot. So, when you get into the
car and you get out, kind of just like
just like fry your leg as you put it
there. So, I've learned my lesson. A
couple people have gotten tattoos there.
Yeah. You can't really see it, but it's
like It's like there. But look, this is
actually the original color of the car.
A lot of people were curious what was
the actual color of the car.
That's it right there. I don't know if
you could kind of really tell, but it's
like a navy dark dark dark dark dark
blue.
It's a the launch edition Bugatti.
There's only I think one of these in the
world in this specific spec. You know,
when they launched the Pure Sport Yeah.
This is the launch edition. This is what
This This This was the example of the
Bugatti Pure Sport.
Now it's the example of the Bugatti Pure
Sport. So It's the only example.
>> The only example of the Bugatti Pure
Sport. Honestly, guys,
I'm not a mechanic.
I'm just a trader and someone that likes
to drive cars. I am not a car
connoisseur, enthusiast. Like I don't
know what any of this is right
here. Yeah, there's a There's a lot of
wires not even connected like
Like how's this car even on right now?
Honestly, I will say this, I've driven
many cars in the past and with the
smallest disconnect or a fuse that goes
out, the vehicle does not work. The fact
that this car was literally split in
half at one point, like completely in
half, and that it was put back together,
it has no headlights, no body panels,
the old the sensors here in the front
that it feels like if you're going to
get close to something, doesn't have a
windshield, doesn't have nothing, and
it's running and driving like if the car
was perfectly fully built, I give props
to Bugatti. I'm not going to lie. They
built an amazing car. They really did. I
have to give my props to them because
any car, any Rivolta, any McLaren, any
Lamborghini, if it's this disassembled,
it will never be as drivable as
functional as this is right now. There's
just no way. I mean, yes, the entire
dash is on. Like every possible check
engine light is on, but we can go take
this on the highway right now and smoke
99% of the cars on the road right now.
That will cost with no windshield.
>> Bro, that's a rock in your face
that can literally like smash your face.
That would really suck, dude. Now, our
next steps with the Bugatti is pretty
much the final steps. We're just missing
to put the entire car together and paint
it. So, we were thinking of a bunch of
different variations of paint that we
can use, but I believe that this purple
is the identity of the car. And we kind
of just have to stamp the car with the
purple. You know, the interior's purple.
Yeah, we kind of have no other option at
this point.
>> really no like we were thinking of a
crazy color-changing combination. If the
car is this disassembled, might as well
do something that's insane. But at this
point, the purple is the identity of the
car. So, we are going to respray the
entire car. So, all of this is going to
get sanded down. It's all going to get
removed. It's going to get primered, and
then it's going to get repainted. This
wrap that I did a year ago. Also, people
don't know this. You know, I crashed
this car April 13th, 2025. So, I crashed
this car well over a year ago. I only
put it out there on social media like
5-6 months after because I was honestly
embarrassed that I crashed it at the
beginning. But then I accepted and I
embraced it. I turned probably one of
the biggest negatives that can happen to
me in terms of a car and financial
positioning into a crazy journey that I
would have never foreseen myself to be
doing. Fighting with a billion-dollar
company, beefing with a See the CEO of
Bugatti. Like, dude, who are Yeah,
crashing this car was probably the best
thing that's ever happened to us.
You know how much money I lost?
I lost a lot of money, bro.
But you know what? It's fine. It's the
name of the game, bro. I will be
remembered as the guy that
bought a Bugatti,
crashed the Bugatti,
made the CEO look like a
put it back together
without the help of Matt Armstrong,
and
>> [laughter]
>> and take it to the track and do 220 mph
again. 222
mph again. That's the fastest I've ever
been in this car. It was 220 222
in Mexico.
What you just tell me? Yeah, I want to
do the backflip off the tire, bro. When
was the last time you did a backflip
after the trip?
>> At Jake Paul's ranch, but I've never
done it off I I did it off a platform
into water.
And I failed every time.
Can you spot me real quick? Oh, let's do
it on my other bug.
I forgot him, bug.
>> This is still with me, bro.
Yeah, I think it's good. Yeah.
Do you Do you know how to spot me or
not?
Isn't it something like like that?
>> Yeah.
We should get another guy, no? You're
pretty happy.
No, you got me. All right, if you say
so. Wait, let me spot you first. You
think you got it or not? No, I tried it
the other day and I [laughter] fell on
my head. Three, two, one.
I didn't even jump.
>> Sover, you didn't even Yeah, that's what
I'm saying. You didn't even jump. You
know you got to fail once. Two, three.
>> [laughter]
>> Bro, bro, you're not even jumping, bro.
You're like jumping and QUITTING
HALFWAY, BRO.
>> [laughter]
[screaming]
>> WOO! I WANT TO HAPPEN TO YOU. YOU GOT
THIS. ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO. LET'S ONE,
TWO, THREE.
>> [laughter]
>> Hit him, guys. Bro, I'm flopping so bad,
bro. I'm like We need to clean the car
in back. You're going to help us with
something. We got a special guest. He
doesn't know why he brought a towel, but
it's all going to make sense right now.
Someone's going to bleed.
>> [laughter]
>> I used to be ESL. Did you know that?
Today we're teaching the boys how to
back flip. So I started off by showing
proper back flip forms. Everybody had an
example to follow. Then a few practice
jumps and using my special towel
technique, you show the participant that
they're safe and they can't fall on
their head even if they do everything
wrong.
Even if we do everything wrong, so don't
this up.
Bro, we just have people spawning.
>> [laughter]
>> You said I said back flip? Yeah.
No way.
Contra
The Volkswagen?
It won't break? No, it won't break. No
way, it will break. It won't break.
It won't break.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah, bro.
You'll teach me how to do that.
>> [laughter]
>> Okay.
Okay.
ONE, TWO.
>> [laughter]
>> ALL RIGHT, READY? ALL RIGHT, READY?
ONE, TWO, THREE.
ONE,
TWO, THREE.
>> [laughter]
>> LET'S GO AGAIN. LET'S GO [laughter]
AGAIN.
LET'S GO AGAIN.
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> ALL ALL LET'S GO AGAIN.
COME ON. 1 2
Yeah.
All right, let's go again.
That's it, bro.
>> [laughter]
>> Let me try that drone out.
They already like ready for your weight
that they're going to grab me and just
throw me.
Dude, it looks so cool, bro.
>> [laughter]
>> It's like too much
That's what I'm saying, dude.
>> [laughter]
>> Bro, I'm telling you, bro. It's like
It's like a weird feeling, bro.
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
[applause]
>> It's hard, bro. It's hard, dude.
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> Set it and forget. Like, comment, and
subscribe. Set it and forget.
>> [laughter]
>> Like, comment Like, comment Subscribe.
Subscribe.
Yeah, bro.
>> [laughter]
>> See you boys in the next one. See you.
>> [music]
[music]